Guide to the Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- ALPHABETICAL LISTING OF SCRIPTS BY PROGRAM TITLES
  - OLDSMOBILE MUSIC THEATER
    Producer: Jacqueline Babbin
    Director: Jack Smight
    Writer: Irving Gaynor Neiman
    - Episode #1, 1959 Mar 26 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Episode #6, 1959 May 7 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - OMNIBUS
    Drama and literature, with Alistair Cooke.
    Producer: Fred Rickey
    Directors: Bob Banner, Mel Ferrer, Andrew McCullough, Cyril Ritchard, Bob Miller, Don Hewitt, Delbert Mann, John Stix, Jeffrey Hayden
    (Author, where known, and in some cases title, listed after date)
    - 135th Street ("Blue Monday Blues") George Gershwin, 1953 Mar 29 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - The Abracadabra Kid William Saroyan, 1953 Apr 19 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - The Battler Arnold Schulman, 1953 Oct 11 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - King Lear (with Orson Welles) Peter Brook, 1953 Oct 18 (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Arnold Schulman, 1953 Oct 25 (Box 279, Folder 7)
    - G. B. Shaw, 1953 Nov 1 (Box 279, Folder 8)
    - Susan Glaspell, Elizabeth Hart, 1953 Nov 8 (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - George Bellak, 1953 Nov 15 (Box 279, Folder 10)
    - Maurice Valency, 1953 Nov 22 (Box 279, Folder 11)
    - Arnold Schulman, 1953 Dec 6 (Box 279, Folder 12)
    - Moss Hart, 1953 Dec 13 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Carson McCullers, 1953 Dec 27 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Arnold Sundgaard, Tad Mosel, 1954 Jan 3 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Ted Mosel, 1954 Jan 10 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - 1954 Jan 24 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Arnold Schulman, 1954 Jan 31 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - 1954 Feb 7 (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Budd Schulberg, 1954 Feb 14 (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - 1954 Feb 21 (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - Alfred Sutro, A.K. Lewis, 1954 Feb 28 (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - 1954 Mar 7 (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - James Thomas Flexner, 1954 Mar 14 (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - Maurice Valency, 1954 Mar 28 (Box 280, Folder 13)
    - Fred Allen, Jack Roche, 1954 Oct 17 (Box 280, Folder 14)
    - Joel Sayre, 1954 Oct 31 (Box 280, Folder 15)
    - John Gassner, Ed Jurist, 1954 Dec 19 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - 1955 Jan 23 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Hamlet Shakespeare, 1955 Jan 30 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - James Flexner, 1955 Feb 27 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Robert Coughlan, 1955 Oct 9 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Alvin Sapinsley, 1957 Jan 20 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - John Latouche, 1957 Feb 10 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - E.J. Kahn, 1957 Feb 17 (Box 281, Folder 8)
    - The Boyhood of William Shakespeare Walter Kerr Alfred Harbage, 1957 Feb 24 (Box 281, Folder 9)
    - Alvin Sapinsley, 1957 Mar 10 (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - 1957 Mar 17 (Box 281, Folder 11)
    - 1957 Mar 24 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - 1957 Nov 3 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - 1957 Nov 17 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - James Lee, 1958 Oct 26 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Nicholas Baehr, 1958 Nov 9 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - James Agee, 1959 Feb 1 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - (with score by Virgil Thompson), 1959 Mar 29 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - H.L. Tredree, 1959 Apr 12 (Box 282, Folder 7)
    - 1960 Nov 13 (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - 1960 Dec 11 (Box 282, Folder 9)
    - 1961 Jan 1 (Box 282, Folder 10)
    - 1961 Apr 16 (Box 282, Folder 11)
    - fragment (Box 282, Folder 12)
  - ON TRIAL
    Writers: Don Mankiewicz, Paul David, Larry Marcus, Stuart Miller, Merwin Gerard, Irving Rubine
    (No air date indicated; catalogued in order of script date)
    - 1956 May 11 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - 1956 July 9 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - 1956 Jul 18 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - 1956 Aug 13 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - 1956 Aug 14 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - 1956 Aug 17 (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - 1956 Sep 24 (Box 283, Folder 7)
    - 1956 Sep 26 (Box 283, Folder 8)
    - 1956 Sep 27 (Box 283, Folder 9)
    - 1956 Oct 24 (Box 283, Folder 10)
    - 1956 Nov 15 (Box 283, Folder 11)
    - 1957 Feb 11 (Box 283, Folder 12)
    - 1957 Mar 14 (Box 283, Folder 13)
    - 1957 Apr 3 (Box 283, Folder 14)
    - 1957 Apr 26 (Box 283, Folder 15)
  - OPEN END
    - David Susskind, Jackie Gleason, 1962 Jan 7 (Box 283, Folder 16)
    - Marlon Brando, Eugene Burdick, George Englund, 1963 Apr 21 (Box 283, Folder 17)
  - OUR AMERICAN HERITAGE
    History
    - Not in Vain Richard Goldhurst, 1961 Apr 1 (Box 283, Folder 18)
  - OUR MISS BROOKS
    Producer: Larry Burns
    Directors: Al Lewis, John Claar, John Rich
    Writers: Al Lewis, Joe Quillan, Arthur Alsberg
    (All dates indicated are film dates, not necessarily air dates)
    - Episode #93, 1955 Feb 22 (Box 283, Folder 19)
    - Episode #94, 1955 Mar 8 (Box 283, Folder 20)
    - Episode #95, 1955 Mar 15 (Box 283, Folder 21)
    - Episode #96, 1955 Mar 22 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Episode #97, 1955 Mar 29 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Episode #98, 1955 Apr 5 (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - Episode #99, 1955 Apr 19 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Episode #101, 1955 Sep 13 (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Episode #102, 1955 Sep 20 (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Episode #104 (2 copies), 1955 Oct 4 (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - Episode #105 (2 copies), 1955 Oct 11 (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - Episode #106, 1955 Oct 18 (Box 284, Folder 9)
    - Episode #108, 1955 Nov 1 (Box 284, Folder 10)
    - Episode #109, undated (Box 284, Folder 11)
    - Episode #112, undated (Box 284, Folder 12)
    - Episode #113, 1955 Dec 6 (Box 284, Folder 13)
    - Episode #116, 1956 Jan 3 (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - Episode #117, undated (Box 284, Folder 15)
    - Episode #118, undated (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Episode #119, undated (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - Episode #120, undated (Box 285, Folder 3)
    - Episode #121, undated (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - Episode #122, undated (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - Episode #123, undated (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - Episode #124, undated (Box 285, Folder 7)
    - Episode #125, undated (Box 285, Folder 8)
    - Episode #129, undated (Box 285, Folder 9)
    - Episode #130, undated (Box 285, Folder 10)
  - OUTLOOK (Box 285)
    - 1958 May 25 (Box 285, Folder 11)
  - PAT BOONE CHEVY SHOWROOM
    Music, comedy, variety
    See also "The Chevy Showroom"
    Producers: Joseph Soutley
    Directors: Frank Satinstein, Tom Naud, Bill Hobin, Bill Hobin, David Geisel, Dan Lownsbery
    Writers: Selma Diamond, Bill Jacobson, Jerry Seelen, Woody Allen, Bill Gammie, Chuck Horner, Tony Webster, Artie Malvin, Larry Gelbart
    - Episode #1, 1957 Oct 3 (Box 285, Folder 12)
    - Episode #2, 1957 Oct 10 (Box 285, Folder 13)
    - Episode #5, 1957 Oct 31 (Box 285, Folder 14)
    - Episode #7, 1957 Nov 14 (Box 285, Folder 15)
    - Episode #8, 1957 Nov 21 (Box 285, Folder 16)
    - Episode #9, 1957 Nov 28 (Box 285, Folder 17)
    - Episode #11, 1957 Dec 12 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Episode #12, 1957 Dec 19 (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - Episode #13, 1957 Dec 26 (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Episode #16, 1958 Jan 16 (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Episode #19, 1958 Feb 6 (Box 286, Folder 5)
    - Episode #23, 1958 Mar 6 (Box 286, Folder 6)
    - Episode #30, 1958 Apr 24 (Box 286, Folder 7)
    - Episode #33, 1958 May 15 (Box 286, Folder 8)
    - Episode #34, 1958 May 22 (Box 286, Folder 9)
    - Episode #35, 1958 May 29 (Box 286, Folder 10)
    - Episode #37, 1958 Jun 12 (Box 286, Folder 11)
    - Episode #39, 1958 Jun 26 (Box 286, Folder 12)
    - 1958 Oct 2 (Box 286, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Oct 9 (Box 286, Folder 14)
    - 1958 Oct 16 (Box 286, Folder 15)
    - 1958 Oct 23 (Box 286, Folder 16)
    - 1958 Oct 30 (Box 286, Folder 17)
    - 1958 Nov 6 (Box 286, Folder 18)
    - 1958 Nov 13 (Box 286, Folder 19)
    - 1958 Nov 20 (Box 286, Folder 20)
    - 1958 Nov 27 (Box 286, Folder 21)
    - 1958 Dec 4 (Box 286, Folder 22)
    - 1958 Dec 11 (Box 286, Folder 23)
    - 1958 Dec 25 (Box 286, Folder 24)
    - 1959 Jan 1 (Box 286, Folder 25)
    - 1959 Jan 8 (Box 286, Folder 26)
    - 1959 Jan 15 (Box 286, Folder 27)
    - 1959 Jan 22 (Box 286, Folder 28)
    - 1959 Jan 29 (Box 286, Folder 29)
    - 1959 Feb 5 (2 copies) (Box 286, Folder 30)
    - 1959 Feb 12 (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - 1959 Feb 19 (2 copies) (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - 1959 Mar 5 (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - 1959 Mar 12 (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - 1959 Mar 19 (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - 1959 Mar 26 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - 1959 Apr 2 (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - 1959 Apr 9 (Box 287, Folder 8)
    - 1959 Apr 16 (Box 287, Folder 9)
    - 1959 Apr 23 (Box 287, Folder 10)
    - 1959 Apr 30 (Box 287, Folder 11)
    - 1959 May 7 (Box 287, Folder 12)
    - 1959 May 14 (Box 287, Folder 13)
    - 1959 May 21 (Box 287, Folder 14)
    - 1959 Jun 4 (Box 287, Folder 15)
    - 1959 Jun 11 (Box 287, Folder 16)
    - 1959 Jun 18 (Box 287, Folder 17)
    - 1959 Jun 25 (Box 287, Folder 18)
    - 1959 Oct 1 (Box 287, Folder 19)
    - 1959 Oct 8 (Box 287, Folder 20)
    - 1959 Oct 15 (Box 287, Folder 21)
    - 1959 Oct 22 (Box 287, Folder 22)
    - 1959 Oct 29 (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - 1959 Nov 5 (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - 1959 Nov 12 (Box 288, Folder 3)
    - 1959 Nov 26 (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - 1959 Dec 3 (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - 1959 Dec 10 (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - 1959 Dec 24 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - 1959 Dec 31 (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - 1960 Jan 7 (Box 288, Folder 9)
    - 1960 Jan 14 (Box 288, Folder 10)
    - 1960 Jan 21 (Box 288, Folder 11)
    - 1960 Jan 28 (Box 288, Folder 12)
    - 1960 Feb 4 (Box 288, Folder 13)
    - 1960 Feb 11 (Box 288, Folder 14)
    - 1960 Feb 25 (Box 288, Folder 15)
    - 1960 Mar 3 (Box 288, Folder 16)
    - 1960 Mar 10 (Box 288, Folder 17)
    - 1960 Mar 17 (Box 288, Folder 18)
    - 1960 Mar 24 (Box 288, Folder 19)
    - 1960 Mar 31 (Box 288, Folder 20)
    - 1960 May 19 (Box 288, Folder 21)
    - 1960 May 26 (Box 288, Folder 22)
    - 1960 Jun 2 (Box 288, Folder 23)
    - 1960 Jun 16 (Box 288, Folder 24)
    - 1960 Jun 23 (Box 288, Folder 25)
    - (13 undated fragments) (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - THE PATRICE MUNSEL SHOW
    Producer-Director: Clark Jones
    Writers: Larry Gelbart, Sheldon Keller
    - 1957 Oct 4 (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - 1957 Nov 15 (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - 1957 Dec 13 (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - 1957 Dec 20 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - 1957 Dec 27 (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - 1958 Jan 3 (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - 1958 Jan 10 (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - 1958 Jan 31 (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - 1958 Feb 7 (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - 1958 Feb 14 (Box 289, Folder 11)
    - 1958 Feb 21 (Box 289, Folder 12)
    - 1958 Feb 28 (Box 289, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Mar 7 (Box 289, Folder 14)
    - 1958 Mar 14 (Box 289, Folder 15)
    - 1958 Mar 21 (Box 289, Folder 16)
    - 1958 Apr 4 (Box 289, Folder 17)
    - 1958 Apr 11 (Box 289, Folder 18)
    - 1958 Apr 18 (Box 289, Folder 19)
    - 1958 May 2 (Box 289, Folder 20)
    - 1958 May 16 (Box 289, Folder 21)
    - 1958 May 23 (Box 289, Folder 22)
    - 1958 May 30 (Box 289, Folder 23)
    - 1958 Jun 6 (Box 289, Folder 24)
    - 1958 Jun 13 (Box 289, Folder 25)
    - undated (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - fragments (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - THE PATTI PAGE SHOW
    - 1956 Jun 16 (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Episode #3, 1956 Jun 30 (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - Episode #4, 1956 Jul 7 (Box 290, Folder 5)
  - PENTAGON USA
    Drama
    Writer: Joel Murcott
    - Episode #7, 1953 Sep 17 (Box 290, Folder 6)
  - THE PERRY COMO SHOW
    Producers: Robert S. Finkel
    Directors: Grey Lockwood, Clark Jones
    Writers: Goodman Ace, Mort Green, George Foster, Jay Burton
    - Episode #3, 1955 Oct 1 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - Episode #4, 1955 Oct 8 (Box 290, Folder 8)
    - Episode #12, 1955 Dec 3 (Box 290, Folder 9)
    - Episode #18, 1956 Jan 14 (Box 290, Folder 10)
    - Episode #20, 1956 Jan 28 (Box 290, Folder 11)
    - Episode #22, 1956 Feb 11 (Box 290, Folder 12)
    - Episode #25, 1956 Mar 3 (Box 290, Folder 13)
    - Episode #29, 1956 Mar 31 (Box 290, Folder 14)
    - Episode #31, 1956 Apr 14 (Box 290, Folder 15)
    - Episode #32, 1956 Apr 21 (Box 290, Folder 16)
    - Episode #33, 1956 Apr 28 (Box 290, Folder 17)
    - Episode #34, 1956 May 5 (Box 290, Folder 18)
    - Episode #37 (2 copies), 1956 May 26 (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Episode #38, 1956 Jun 2 (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Episode #39, 1956 Jun 9 (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Episode #41, 1956 Sep 22 (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Episode #42, 1956 Sep 29 (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Episode #43, 1956 Oct 6 (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - Episode #46, 1956 Oct 27 (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - Episode #51, 1956 Dec 1 (Box 291, Folder 8)
    - Episode #52, 1956 Dec 8 (Box 291, Folder 9)
    - Episode #54, 1956 Dec 22 (Box 291, Folder 10)
    - Episode #57, 1957 Jan 12 (Box 291, Folder 11)
    - Episode #58, 1957 Jan 19 (Box 291, Folder 12)
    - Episode #59, 1957 Jan 26 (Box 291, Folder 13)
    - Episode #60, 1957 Feb 2 (Box 291, Folder 14)
    - Episode #61, 1957 Feb 9 (Box 291, Folder 15)
    - Episode #62, 1957 Feb 16 (Box 291, Folder 16)
    - Episode #63, 1957 Feb 23 (Box 291, Folder 17)
    - Episode #64, 1957 Mar 2 (Box 291, Folder 18)
    - Episode #65, 1957 Mar 9 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Episode #66, 1957 Mar 16 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Episode #67, 1957 Mar 23 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Episode #68, 1957 Mar 30 (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Episode #69, 1957 Apr 6 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Episode #70, 1957 Apr 13 (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Episode #71, 1957 Apr 20 (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Episode #72, 1957 Apr 27 (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Episode #73, 1957 May 4 (Box 292, Folder 9)
    - Episode #75, 1957 May 18 (Box 292, Folder 10)
    - Episode #77, 1957 Jun 1 (Box 292, Folder 11)
    - Episode #79, 1957 Sep 14 (Box 292, Folder 12)
    - Episode #81, 1957 Sep 21 (Box 292, Folder 13)
    - Episode #81, 1957 Sep 28 (Box 292, Folder 14)
    - Episode #82, 1957 Oct 5 (Box 292, Folder 15)
    - Episode #83, 1957 Oct 12 (Box 292, Folder 16)
    - Episode #85, 1957 Oct 26 (Box 292, Folder 17)
    - Episode #86, 1957 Nov 2 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Episode #88, 1957 Nov 23 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Episode #90, 1957 Dec 7 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Episode #91, 1957 Dec 14 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Episode #92, 1957 Dec 21 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Episode #94, 1958 Jan 4 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Episode #95, 1958 Jan 11 (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - Episode #96, 1958 Jan 18 (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - Episode #97, 1958 Jan 25 (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - Episode #98, 1958 Feb 1 (Box 293, Folder 10)
    - Episode #99, 1958 Feb 8 (Box 293, Folder 11)
    - Episode #100, 1958 Feb 15 (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - Episode #102, 1958 Mar 1 (Box 293, Folder 13)
    - Episode #103, 1958 Mar 8 (Box 293, Folder 14)
    - Episode #104, 1958 Mar 15 (Box 293, Folder 15)
    - Episode #105, 1958 Mar 15 (Box 293, Folder 16)
    - Episode #106, 1958 Mar 29 (Box 293, Folder 17)
    - Episode #107, 1958 Apr 5 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Episode #108, 1958 Apr 12 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Episode #109, 1958 Apr 19 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Episode #111, 1958 May 3 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - Episode #112, 1958 May 10 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Episode #113, 1958 May 17 (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Episode #114, 1958 May 24 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Episode #116, 1958 Jun 7 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Episode #117, 1958 Sep 13 (Box 294, Folder 9)
    - Episode #118, 1958 Sep 20 (Box 294, Folder 10)
    - Episode #119, 1958 Sep 27 (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - Episode #120, 1958 Oct 4 (Box 294, Folder 12)
    - Episode #121, 1958 Oct 11 (Box 294, Folder 13)
    - Episode #122, 1958 Oct 18 (Box 294, Folder 14)
    - Episode #123, 1958 Oct 25 (Box 294, Folder 15)
    - Episode #124, 1958 Nov 1 (Box 294, Folder 16)
    - Episode #125, 1958 Nov 8 (Box 294, Folder 17)
    - Episode #126, 1958 Nov 15 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Episode #127, 1958 Nov 22 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Episode #128, 1958 Nov 29 (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Episode #129, 1958 Dec 6 (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Episode #130, 1958 Dec 13 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Episode #131, 1958 Dec 20 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Episode #132, 1958 Dec 27 (Box 295, Folder 7)
    - Episode #133, 1959 Jan 3 (Box 295, Folder 8)
    - Episode #134, 1959 Jan 10 (Box 295, Folder 9)
    - Episode #135, 1959 Jan17 (Box 295, Folder 10)
    - Episode #136, 1959 Jan 24 (Box 295, Folder 11)
    - Episode #137, 1959 Jan 31 (Box 295, Folder 12)
    - Episode #138, 1959 Feb 7 (Box 295, Folder 13)
    - Episode #139, 1959 Feb 14 (Box 295, Folder 14)
    - Episode #140, 1959 Feb 21 (Box 295, Folder 15)
    - Episode #141, 1959 Feb 28 (Box 295, Folder 16)
    - Episode #142, 1959 Mar 7 (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Episode #143, 1959 Mar 14 (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - Episode #145, 1959 Mar 28 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Episode #146, 1959 Apr 4 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Episode #147, 1959 Apr 11 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Episode #148, 1959 Apr 18 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - Episode #150, 1959 May 2 (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - Episode #151, 1959 May 9 (Box 296, Folder 8)
    - Episode #152, 1959 May 16 (Box 296, Folder 9)
    - Episode #153, 1959 May 23 (Box 296, Folder 10)
    - Episode #154, 1959 May 30 (Box 296, Folder 11)
    - Episode #155, 1959 Jun 6 (Box 296, Folder 12)
  - PERRY COMO'S KRAFT MUSIC HALL
    Apparently the replacement for "The Perry Como Show," as this show is almost identical in format.
    Producers: Nick Vanhoff
    Directors: Dwight Hemion, Clark Jones, Marlo Lewis
    Writers: Goodman Ace, Buz Kohan, Selma Diamond, Herb Sargent, Jay Burton, Art Baer, Frank Peppiatt, Ben Joelson, John Aylesworth, Will Glickman, Herbert Baker, Bill Angelos, Billy Friedberg
    - Episode #156, 1959 Sep 30 (Box 296, Folder 13)
    - Episode #157, 1959 Oct 7 (Box 296, Folder 14)
    - Episode #158, 1959 Oct 14 (Box 296, Folder 15)
    - Episode #159, 1959 Oct 21 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Episode #160, 1959 Oct 28 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Episode #161, 1959 Nov 11 (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - Episode #162, 1959 Nov 18 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - Episode #163 (2 copies), 1959 Nov 25 (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - Episode #164, 1959 Dec 2 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Episode #165, 1959 Dec 9 (Box 297, Folder 7)
    - Episode #166, 1959 Dec 16 (Box 297, Folder 8)
    - Episode #167, 1959 Dec 23 (Box 297, Folder 9)
    - Episode #168, 1959 Dec 30 (Box 297, Folder 10)
    - Episode #169, 1960 Jan 6 (Box 297, Folder 11)
    - Episode #170 (2 copies), 1960 Jan 20 (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Episode #171 (2 copies), 1960 Jan 27 (Box 298, Folder 2)
    - Episode #172, 1960 Feb 3 (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - Episode #173, 1960 Feb 10 (Box 298, Folder 4)
    - Episode #174, 1960 Feb 17 (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - Episode #175, 1960 Feb 24 (Box 298, Folder 6)
    - Episode #176, 1960 Mar 2 (Box 298, Folder 7)
    - Episode #177, 1960 Mar 9 (Box 298, Folder 8)
    - Episode #178 (2 copies), 1960 Mar 16 (Box 298, Folder 9)
    - Episode #179, 1960 Mar 23 (Box 298, Folder 10)
    - Episode #180 (2 copies), 1960 Mar 30 (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - Episode #181, 1960 Apr 6 (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Episode #182 (2 copies), 1960 Apr 13 (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Episode #183 (2 copies), 1960 Apr 27 (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Episode #184 (2 copies), 1960 May 4 (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - Episode #185 (2 copies), 1960 May 11 (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - Episode #186 (2 copies), 1960 May 18 (Box 299, Folder 7)
    - Episode #187 (2 copies), 1960 May 25 (Box 299, Folder 8)
    - Episode #189, 1960 Oct 5 (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Episode #190 (2 copies), 1960 Oct 12 (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Episode #191, 1960 Oct 19 (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Episode #192, 1960 Oct 26 (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - Episode #193, 1960 Nov 2 (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - Episode #194 (2 copies), 1960 Nov 9 (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Episode #195, 1960 Nov 23 (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - Episode #196, 1960 Nov 30 (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - Episode #195, 1960 Dec 7 (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - 1960 Dec 14 (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - Episode #200, 1960 Dec 28 (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Episode #201, 1961 Jan 3 (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - Episode #202, 1961 Jan 18 (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Episode #203, 1961 Jan 25 (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Episode #204, 1961 Feb 1 (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Episode #206, 1961 Feb 15 (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Episode #207, 1961 Feb 22 (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - Episode #208, 1961 Mar 1 (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Episode #209, 1961 Mar 8 (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - Episode #210, 1961 Mar 15 (Box 301, Folder 10)
    - Episode #211, 1961 Mar 22 (Box 301, Folder 11)
    - Episode #212, 1961 Mar 29 (Box 301, Folder 12)
    - Episode #213, 1961 Apr 5 (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Episode #214, 1961 Apr 19 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - Episode #215, 1961 Apr 27 (Box 302, Folder 3)
    - Episode #216, 1961 May 3 (Box 302, Folder 4)
    - Episode #217, 1961 May 10 (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - Episode #218, 1961 May 17 (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - Episode #219, 1961 May 24 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - Episode #220 (2 copies), 1961 May 31 (Box 302, Folder 8)
    - Episode #221, 1961 Jun 7 (Box 302, Folder 9)
    - Episode #222, 1961 Oct 4 (Box 302, Folder 10)
    - Episode #223, 1961 Oct 11 (Box 302, Folder 11)
    - Episode #224, 1960 Oct 18 (Box 302, Folder 12)
    - Episode #225, 1961 Oct 25 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - Episode #226, 1961 Nov 1 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - Episode #227, 1961 Nov 8 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - Episode #228, 1961 Nov 15 (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - Episode #229, 1961 Nov 22 (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - Episode #230, 1961 Dec 6 (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - Episode #231, 1961 Dec 20 (Box 303, Folder 7)
    - Episode #232, 1961 Dec 27 (Box 303, Folder 8)
    - Episode #233, 1962 Jan 3 (Box 303, Folder 9)
    - Episode #234, 1962 Jan 10 (Box 303, Folder 10)
    - Episode #235, 1962 Jan 17 (Box 303, Folder 11)
    - Episode #236, 1962 Feb 7 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - Episode #237, 1962 Feb 14 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - Episode #238, 1962 Feb 21 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - Episode #239, 1962 Mar 7 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Episode #240, 1962 Mar 14 (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Episode #241, 1962 Mar 21 (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Episode #242, 1962 Mar 28 (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - Episode #243, 1962 Apr 4 (Box 304, Folder 8)
    - Episode #245, 1962 May 2 (Box 304, Folder 9)
    - Episode #246, 1962 May 9 (Box 304, Folder 10)
    - Episode #247, 1962 May 16 (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Episode #248, 1962 May 23 (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - Episode #249, 1962 May 30 (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - Episode #250, 1962 Jun 6 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - Episode #251, 1962 Oct 3 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Episode #252, 1962 Oct 10 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - Episode #253, 1962 Oct 17 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Episode #256, 1962 Nov 14 (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - Episode #257, 1962 Nov 21 (Box 305, Folder 9)
    - Episode #259, 1962 Nov 28 (Box 305, Folder 10)
    - Episode #260, 1962 Dec 5 (Box 305, Folder 11)
    - Episode #261, 1962 Dec 19 (Box 305, Folder 12)
    - Episode #262, 1962 Dec 26 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - Episode #263, 1963 Jan 2 (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - Episode #264, 1963 Jan 9 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - Episode #266 (2 copies), 1963 Jan 30 (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - Episode #267, 1963 Feb 6 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Episode #269 (2 copies), 1963 Feb 20 (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - Episode #270, 1963 Feb 27 (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - Episode #271, 1963 Mar 6 (Box 306, Folder 8)
    - Episode #272 (2 copies), 1963 Mar 20 (Box 306, Folder 9)
    - Episode #273, 1963 Mar 27 (Box 306, Folder 10)
    - Episode #274, 1963 Apr 3 (Box 306, Folder 11)
    - Episode #275, 1963 Apr 10 (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - Episode #277, 1963 Apr 24 (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - Episode #278, 1963 May 1 (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - Episode #279, 1963 May 8 (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - Episode #280, 1963 May 22 (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - Episode #282, 1963 Jun 5 (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - Episode #284, 1963 Oct 3 (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - Episode #285, 1963 Nov 21 (Box 307, Folder 8)
    - Episode #286, 1964 Jan 23 (Box 307, Folder 9)
  - PERRY PRESENTS
    Producer: Ray Charles
    Director: Stan Harris
    Writers: Allan Sherman, Joe Cook, Andy Rooney
    - Episode #1, 1959 Jun 13 (Box 307, Folder 10)
    - Episode #2, 1959 Jun 20 (Box 307, Folder 11)